

# NUR HAZIRAH ABDULLAH



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/NURHAZIRAHABDULLAH/



# ABOUT ME

A fresh graduate of Netcentric Computing that is equipped with a vast programming language especially in PHP, SQL, HTML, Java, and Javascript. Experienced in gathering requirements, analysing data, and doing documentations. A meticulous person and diligent worker that possesses good analytical and problem-solving skills.

Expected Salary: RM 2,800 - RM 3,200



# **CONTACT**

#### Address:

Seremban, Negeri Sembilan, Malaysia

#### Mobile:

+(60)14 - 9728 202

nurhazirah.abdllh@gmail.com

### Website:

linkedin.com/in/nurhazirahabdullah/ github.com/nhzraa



# **SKILLS**

PHP Android Studio SQL Adobe Illustrator UBS Accounting MSSQL MySOL Microsoft Excel HTML Java Analytical Skills

Problem-solving JavaScript Node.js Communication C++ Teamwork



# **LANGUAGES**

Malay (Native)





## **EXPERIENCES**

Internship -Admin Sales cum **Graphic Designer** 

(Jul 2020 - Aug 2020) Acid Cubic Enterprise

Perform administrative tasks such as making quotations, tax invoices, delivery orders and cash bills. Acted as a shopkeeper and interacted with the customers. Uses UBS Accounting System to key-in company's data. Made product artworks using Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop.

Internship -**IPQA Trainee**  Nexperia Malaysia Sdn Bhd (Feb 2020 - Jul 2020)

Develop and enhance QA PPM 2.0 Webpage (Language used: MSSQL, PHP, HTML). Managed to track the data inaccuracy in the PPM 1.0 system and helped to give a possible solution for a more accurate data. Support on data analysis for QA reject trend and SPC data analysis. Support on auditing process for Material Traceability and Collet Check.

Sales Assistant

Fan Feng Sdn Bhd (Jan 2018 - Mar 2018)

Restocked shelves with current products in attractive displays to promote sales. Providing customers with comprehensive assistance throughout product selections

Graphic Designer cum **Software Developer** 

Acid Cubic Enterprise (May 2017 - June 2017)

Used Adobe Illustrator to develop product mock-ups and print materials such as banners, plaques, and medals. Develop a localhost system for the company (Language used: MySQL, PHP, HTML).



# **EDUCATION**

UiTM Jasin, Malacca

BCS (Hons.) of Netcentric Computing (2018 - 2020)

Graduated with CGPA 3.39

Recipient of Dean's List Award in Year 3, Semester 6. Thesis: Recipe Recommendation Application based on Ingredients (Android Studio, MySQL / XAMPP, Node.js) Activities & Societies: Secretariat of Student Representative Council (MPP) UiTM Jasin 2018/2019, Netcentric Club

UiTM Jasin, Malacca

(2015 - 2018)**Diploma of Computer Science** 

Recipient of Dean's List Award in Year 2, Semester 5. Activities & Societies: Photovengers Club, Persatuan Seni Silat Cekak Malaysia (PSSCM), Modern Language Club

(MLS)



# **REFERENCE**

Quality Manager (Nexperia Malaysia) Ms. Lee Chia Ling +6012-674 0928 chia.ling.lee@nexperia.com

Manager (Acid Cubic Enterprise) Mr. Mohd Mukhzani Zakaria +6010-403 1008 acidcubic.8288@gmail.com